Now let's talk about
another service called CodeBuild.
So the name is explicit,
it allows you to build your code in the cloud.
So what does that mean?
That means that the source course is going to be compiled,
the tests are going to be run,
and then the output of which is going to produce packages,
and these packages are going to be ready to be deployed
for example, by CodeDeploy
onto servers so that your application can run.
So, as a diagram, what does it look like?
Well, say your code is in CodeCommit,
CodeBuild is going to retrieve this code from CodeCommit,
run some script that you have to define, build your code,
and then you will have a ready-to-deploy artifacts.
So why would you use CodeBuild?
Well it's fully managed and serverless.
It's continuously scalable and highly available
and secure, and with pay-as-you-go pricing,
that means that you only pay
for the time your code is being built.
There are no servers to manage.
And that means that you can really worry about just coding,
and making sure that a service within AWS,
will take its time to build your code
every single time you push a code updates
into your CodeCommit reupholstery.
So that's it, very simple, I hope you liked it,
and I will see you in the next lecture.